# ABDELRHMAN AHMED ELNHAS

abdelrhman.elnhas1@gmail.com | (+20) 106-927-7066 | linkedin.com/in/abdelrhman-elnhas | Alexandria, Egypt

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am Frontend Web Developer since 2021. I've worked on several projects in various fields. Also, I gained some knowledge about Backend Web Development during working on projects. I am also a UI/UX Designer and a Senior Graphic Designer. I am a hardworking and ambitious individual with a great passion for technology, especially programming.

#### **Contact Information**

- Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/abdelrhman-elnhas
- Behance: https://www.behance.net/aedesigns11
- Github: https://github.com/abdelrhman-elnhas/
- Gmail: Abdelrhman.elnhas1@gmail.com
- Whatsapp: +201069277066

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Master Code | Kafr Elsheikh, Egypt

Frontend Developer | 04/2021 - 07/2023

- Worked on multiple educational websites like :
  - https://francaisbacessam.com
  - https://alemlak-almonofy.com
  - o https://dolphin-in-biology.com

Master Code Landing Page UI/UX Design

http://elawaiel.com

Master Code | Kafr Elsheikh, Egypt **UI/UX Designer** | 06/2022 - 05/2023

- - https://www.behance.net/gallery/160989575/MasterCode-Website-UIUX-Design
  - NileICT Landing Page UI/UX Design
    - https://www.behance.net/gallery/152832487/Nile-ICT-UIUX-Design
  - All Traders Mobile App UI/UX Design
    - https://www.behance.net/gallery/183936541/All-Traders-Mobile-App-UIUX-Design
  - CropCopter Website UI/UX Design
    - https://www.behance.net/gallery/183936663/CropCopter-Website-UIUX-Design

The Sparks Foundation Internship

**Web Developer Intern** | 02/2023 - 03/2023

AE Adv. | ElMahalla Elkubra, Egypt

Graphic Designer | 04/2014 - Present

- Responsible for designing social media designs, logos and all types of advertising printing materials.
  - https://www.behance.net/aedesigns11

### **EDUCATION**

Responsive Web Design, Sololearn

Web Development Fundamentals, Sololearn

CSS, Soloearn

**EF SET** 

EDUCATION	
Degree in Computer Engineering, Faculty of Engineering , Kafr Elsheikh University	07/2023
Computer and Control Systems Department.	
CERTIFICATIONS	
Web-Development Internship, The Sparks Foundation	02/2023
Figma like a pro mixed with UI/UX, Udemy	10/2023
Version Control, Meta	01/2023
Skills Verification Test for Cascading Style Sheets (CSS), HackerRank	12/2022
Git & Github, 365 Data Science	12/2022
Introduction to Python, 365 Data Science	12/2022
Introduction to Frontend Development, Meta	04/2023
UX Design Fundamentals, MaharaTech - ITIMooca	12/2022
HTML and CSS in Depth, Meta	06/2023
React Basics, Meta	08/2023
Introduction to Backend Development, Meta	01/2023
Programming with JavaScript, Meta	05/2023
Introduction to Databases for Backend Development, Meta	04/2023
Programming in Python, Meta	03/2023
JavaScript, Sololearn	12/2022

12/2022

12/2022

12/2022

03/2020

## **Projects**

- cropcopter.net
- francaisbacessam.com
- alemlak-almonofy.com
- dolphin-in-biology.com
- elawaiel.com

## **SKILLS**

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- React.JS
- API
- SASS
- UI Design

- Python
- VCS (Git & Github)
- Laravel
- MySQL
- Adobe XD
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Figma